// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the first custom emoji that chelsB made?', 
      a: ':asana:', 
      b: ':wisco:',
      c: ':nicmoji:',
      d: ':yeti:',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the first custom emoji at clearhead?', 
      a: ':scout:', 
      b: ':fyou:',
      c: ':doge:',
      d: ':party-parrot:',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who made the first custom emoji at clearhead?', 
      a: 'Brendan', 
      b: 'Perica',
      c: 'Haley',
      d: 'Sophie',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many custom emojis does clearhead have?', 
      a: '1339', 
      b: '921',
      c: '1817',
      d: '2198',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Of those 1816, what percentage did chelsB make?', 
      a: '10%', 
      b: '15%',
      c: '20%',
      d: '25%',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who made the :mothership-lasers: emoji?', 
      a: 'Nick B', 
      b: 'West',
      c: 'John',
      d: 'easy-e',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who made the :siren: emoji?', 
      a: 'Couv', 
      b: 'Haley',
      c: 'Marion',
      d: 'Perica',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who made the :maisey-means-business: emoji?', 
      a: 'Molly', 
      b: 'Devon',
      c: 'Libby',
      d: 'Jalaliani',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who made the :party_dead: emoji?', 
      a: 'Jenni', 
      b: 'Joco',
      c: 'Autumn',
      d: 'Billy',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What company will chelsB miss the most?', 
      a: ':classic-accenture:', 
      b: ':clearhead:',
      c: ':svb:',
      d: ':mcmichael-lowe-mcmichael:',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};